[
    {
        "Question": "complaint",
        "Answer": "protest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "complement",
        "Answer": "add to",
        "Options": "supplement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "completely",
        "Answer": "totally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "complex",
        "Answer": "elaborate/ complicated",
        "Options": "system/ made things more difficult"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compilations",
        "Answer": "collections",
        "Options": "put together"
    },
    {
        "Question": "component",
        "Answer": "part/ constituent",
        "Options": "element"
    },
    {
        "Question": "composed of",
        "Answer": "made up of",
        "Options": "created/ mix"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compounded",
        "Answer": "added to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comprehensive",
        "Answer": "thorough/ complete",
        "Options": "understandable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compression",
        "Answer": "crushing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comprise",
        "Answer": "consist of",
        "Options": "make up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compulsorily",
        "Answer": "by requirement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concealed",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": "covered"
    },
    {
        "Question": "concede",
        "Answer": "accept",
        "Options": "admit"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conceiving",
        "Answer": "considering",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concentrate",
        "Answer": "increase the density of population",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concern",
        "Answer": "interest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "concise",
        "Answer": "simple",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conclusive",
        "Answer": "final",
        "Options": "ultimate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conductive to",
        "Answer": "favorable to",
        "Options": "contributive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "configurations",
        "Answer": "arrangements",
        "Options": "shape/ forms"
    },
    {
        "Question": "confined",
        "Answer": "limited to",
        "Options": "restricted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "confront",
        "Answer": "face",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "congeal",
        "Answer": "solidify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "congestion",
        "Answer": "overcrowding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "congregate",
        "Answer": "gather",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conjunction",
        "Answer": "combination",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consecutive",
        "Answer": "successive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consensus",
        "Answer": "agreement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consequence",
        "Answer": "importance",
        "Options": "result"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consequently",
        "Answer": "therefore",
        "Options": "as a result"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conserve",
        "Answer": "save",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consider",
        "Answer": "think about",
        "Options": "view as"
    },
    {
        "Question": "considerable",
        "Answer": "significant/ substantial",
        "Options": "a large amount of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consistent",
        "Answer": "uniform",
        "Options": "regular"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consistently",
        "Answer": "increasingly",
        "Options": "unvarying"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consist of",
        "Answer": "compose of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conspicuous",
        "Answer": "noticeable",
        "Options": "clearly visible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "constant",
        "Answer": "unchanging",
        "Options": "stable/ always"
    },
    {
        "Question": "constellation",
        "Answer": "colleciton",
        "Options": "combination"
    },
    {
        "Question": "constituent",
        "Answer": "component",
        "Options": "comprise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "constrain",
        "Answer": "restrict",
        "Options": "limit"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consult",
        "Answer": "ask",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consumed",
        "Answer": "used up",
        "Options": "eat up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "consumption",
        "Answer": "utilization",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contains",
        "Answer": "includes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contemplate",
        "Answer": "consider",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contends",
        "Answer": "argues",
        "Options": "dispute"
    },
    {
        "Question": "contention",
        "Answer": "debate",
        "Options": "claim"
    },
    {
        "Question": "context",
        "Answer": "environment",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contiguous",
        "Answer": "neighboring",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contradictory",
        "Answer": "conflicting",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "continuous",
        "Answer": "uninterrupted",
        "Options": "constant"
    },
    {
        "Question": "contour",
        "Answer": "outline",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contribute to",
        "Answer": "add to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "contrive",
        "Answer": "create",
        "Options": "invent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "controversial",
        "Answer": "debatable/ conflict",
        "Options": "producing disagreement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conventional",
        "Answer": "usual",
        "Options": "customary/ traditional"
    },
    {
        "Question": "converge",
        "Answer": "come together",
        "Options": "move closer"
    },
    {
        "Question": "convergence",
        "Answer": "gathering",
        "Options": "concentrating"
    },
    {
        "Question": "converge on",
        "Answer": "meet at",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conversely",
        "Answer": "on the other hand",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "converted",
        "Answer": "changed",
        "Options": "transform"
    },
    {
        "Question": "convey",
        "Answer": "communicate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "convict",
        "Answer": "sentence",
        "Options": "condemn"
    },
    {
        "Question": "convinced",
        "Answer": "persuaded",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cope",
        "Answer": "adapt/ deal with",
        "Options": "manage/ handle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "copious",
        "Answer": "abundant",
        "Options": "plentiful"
    },
    {
        "Question": "core",
        "Answer": "center",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "correlate",
        "Answer": "match ",
        "Options": "accord with"
    },
    {
        "Question": "corroborate",
        "Answer": "confirm",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "costly",
        "Answer": "expensive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "countered",
        "Answer": "argued back",
        "Options": "acting against"
    },
    {
        "Question": "counterpart",
        "Answer": "equivalent",
        "Options": "similitude"
    },
    {
        "Question": "countervail",
        "Answer": "oppose",
        "Options": "compensate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "counsel",
        "Answer": "advise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coupled with",
        "Answer": "combined with",
        "Options": "associated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "courses through",
        "Answer": "runs through",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "covered",
        "Answer": "included",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cramped",
        "Answer": "confined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "crawl",
        "Answer": "move",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "create",
        "Answer": "invent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "credible",
        "Answer": "believable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "crest",
        "Answer": "peak",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "crisis",
        "Answer": "critical situation",
        "Options": "disturbance"
    },
    {
        "Question": "criteria",
        "Answer": "standards",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "critical",
        "Answer": "fault-finding",
        "Options": "crucial/ essential"
    },
    {
        "Question": "critically",
        "Answer": "fundamentally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "criticize",
        "Answer": "debate",
        "Options": "find fault"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crude",
        "Answer": "primitive/ unsophisticated",
        "Options": "rough/ initial"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crucial",
        "Answer": "important",
        "Options": "decisively"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crushed",
        "Answer": "ground",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cue",
        "Answer": "hint",
        "Options": "clue"
    },
    {
        "Question": "culminate",
        "Answer": "reach completion",
        "Options": "peak/ climax"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cumbersome",
        "Answer": "burdensome",
        "Options": "clumsy"
    },
    {
        "Question": "curb",
        "Answer": "control",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "curious",
        "Answer": "strange",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "current",
        "Answer": "present",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cushioned",
        "Answer": "protected",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dam",
        "Answer": "block",
        "Options": ""
    }
]